当我们学习响应式设计时候，我们可以看到
When we were learning that response in design, we saw that
常见的模式都是使用 master detail flow，就和我们
a common pattern was to use the master detail flow, which
将要在sunshine这个应用中使用的一样。这是在平板上的
is what were going to use for sunshine. Here are the
效果。在左边有forecast列表，
tablet mocks. We have a list of forecasts on the left, and
当选中它们的时候，我们可以在右边看到详细的信息格子
then for the selected item, we see the detail pane on
无论是纵向还是横向，这种方法都适用于
the right. This applies for a seven inch and ten inch tablets.
7英寸和十英寸的平板电脑。在纵向模式下，列项
Both portrait and landscape orientations. In portrait mode, the columns are
只是有一点点窄而已，但它仍然是两个窗口的UI界面
just a little bit narrower, but it's still a two pane UI.
这些都会在main activity下实现
In terms of implementation, all of this will be under the
在左边是forecast fragment
main activity. Then on the left, we have the forecast fragment.
在右边是detail fragment
And then on the right, we have the detail fragment. On
而在手机上，我们在main activity下只有左边的这个预报列表
the phone, we would still have the main activity with the list
当选中其中的一个项时，会跳转到
of forecast. And then selecting an item would still launch the
detail activity。这是另一种展示方式。在平板电脑上，
detail activity. Here's another way to visualize it. On the tablet, we
在一个activity上有两个紧接着的fragment，而在手机上
have two fragments side by side under one activity. And then
我们的第一个activity包含了第一个fragment
on the phone, we have the first activity containing the first fragment.
当选中了一个项后，会跳转到包含第二个fragment的activity
Selecting an item will launch the second activity containing the second
我们将把这些分成多个编码任务
fragment. We're going to break this up into multiple coding tasks until
直到我们建立最后一个layout布局。首先，我们为平板电脑建立两个
we build up the final layout. First we'll build up the
窗口UI界面。接下来我们将两个fragment
two pane UI for tablets. Then we'll hook up the communication
之间进行通信，即选择一项在右边的窗口
between the two fragments, so that's selecting an item replaces the
显示详细信息。接着我们会学习如何
detail pane on the right. Then we'll learn how to show
在一个被选中项上展示其状态，所以
an activated state on the currently selected item, so we know
我们就会知道详细信息与哪一个相对应。我们还需要确保
what the details pane corresponds to. We'll also need to make
滚动的位置被维持在一个方向
sure that the scroll position is maintained across
上变化。做完这些以后，我们将更新detail layout
orientation changes. After that, we'll update the detail layout
去优化这些更宽的屏幕。
so it's optimized for these wider screens. And
然后，我们将修改adapter所以在这里，“今天”的布局和
then we'll modify the adapter so that today's layout
“其他天”的布局看起来是一样的。在平板上，“today”的布局
looks like the other days. There's no special
并没有什么特殊之处。所以充满希望的是
today layout on the tablet. So hopefully it's clear
我们如何实现这个在平板上的表现行为的思路是很清晰的
how we're going to approach implementing this tablet behavior and
我们将会一个接一个地去慢慢实现
we're going to step through it slowly, one by one